A Guide to the Virginia Electric and Power Company Records, 1849-ca. 1995
Library of Virginia
- Advertisements, 1955-1970, Approx. .65 cubic feet. (Map-case G-14, Drawer 19-20)
  Chiefly contains publicity broadsides created by VEPCO and VEPCO's advertising contractor Cargill, Wilson and Acree for publication as posters and in newspapers, magazines, and other printed material. These advertisements generally promote the expanded use of electrical household appliances, the purchase of electrically operated homes, and the conversion to electrical agricultural equipment by farmers.
  Chronologically.
  - Advertisements, 1955 (Map-case G-14, Drawer 19, Folder 1)
  - Advertisements, 1956 (Map-case G-14, Drawer 19, Folder 2)
  - Advertisements, 1957 (Map-case G-14, Drawer 19, Folder 3)
  - Advertisements, 1958 (Map-case G-14, Drawer 19, Folder 4)
  - Advertisements, 1959 (Map-case G-14, Drawer 19, Folder 5)
  - Advertisements, 1960 (Map-case G-14, Drawer 19, Folder 6)
  - Advertisements, 1961 (Map-case G-14, Drawer 19, Folder 7)
  - Advertisements, 1962 (Map-case G-14, Drawer 19, Folder 8)
  - Advertisements, 1963 (Map-case G-14, Drawer 19, Folder 9)
  - Advertisements (Oversize), 1963 (Map-case 40, Drawer 9, Folder N/A)
    High-rise banner
  - Advertisements, 1964 (Map-case G-14, Drawer 19, Folder 10)
  - Advertisements, 1965 (Map-case G-14, Drawer 20, Folder 1)
  - Advertisements, 1966 (Map-case G-14, Drawer 20, Folder 2)
  - Advertisements, 1967 (Map-case G-14, Drawer 20, Folder 3)
  - Advertisements, 1968 (Map-case G-14, Drawer 20, Folder 4)
  - Advertisements, 1969 (Map-case G-14, Drawer 20, Folder 5)
  - Advertisements, 1970 (Map-case G-14, Drawer 20, Folder 6)
  - Advertisements, n. d. (Map-case G-14, Drawer 20, Folder 7)
- Scrapbooks, 1905-1969, Approx. 3.375 cubic feet. (Box 62)
  Volumes of clippings from Virginia newspapers concerning VEPCO and its subsidiary companies.
  - Electric power rate increase, 1969 (Box 62, Folder 1-2)
  - Miscellaneous newspaper clippings, 1925-1926 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous newspaper clippings, February-October 1921
  - Miscellaneous newspaper clippings, October 1921-December 1922
  - Miscellaneous newspaper clippings, December 1922-October 1923
  - Miscellaneous newspaper clippings concerning the Norfolk and Portsmouth Traction Company, 18 July 1906-30 September 1906
  - Miscellaneous newspaper clippings concerning VEPCO, 1945-1946
  - Miscellaneous newspaper clippings concerning the Virginia Public Service Company, 26 April 1933-4 February 1939
  - Miscellaneous newspaper clippings concerning the Virginia Public Service Company, 25 August 1939-17 November 1939
  - Miscellaneous newspaper clippings concerning the Virginia Railway and Power Company, 5 August 1905-24 November 1906
  - Miscellaneous newspaper clippings concerning the Virginia Railway and Light Company, 14 October 1923-13 November 1924
- Memorabilia, undated, Approx. .35 cubic feet. (Box 63-66)
  Contains insulators, embossers for VEPCO subsidiaries, and an award medal issued in 1966 to VEPCO by the Freedoms Foundation at Valley Forge.
  Arranged by material type. (FRAGILE HANDLE WITH CARE)
- Minute books and ledgers, 1849-1952
  These are account books, cash journals, board of directors' and stockholders' minute books, by-laws, stock ledgers, receivers' registers, and other general ledgers for VEPCO and its subsidiaries. Numbers in parentheses are an anitquated and undeciphered numbering system employed by VEPCO.
  Arranged alphabetically and then chronologically.
  - Alexandria County Lighting Company, minute book (2 J-1), 1911-1918 (Volume 1)
  - Alexandria County Lighting Company, minute book (2 J-2), 1919-1926 (Volume 2)
  - Appomattox Light and Power Company, board of directors' and stockholders' minute book (5 J-1), 1923-1927 (Volume 3)
  - Arlington Electric Company, board of directors' minute book (6 J2-1), 1911-1922 (Volume 4)
  - Arlington Electric Company, stockholders' minute book (6 J1-1), 1911-1918 (Volume 5)
  - Atlantic Coast Terminal Company, minute book (7), 1905 (Volume 6)
  - Atlantic Coast Terminal Company, minute book (7a), 1906-1920 (Volume 7)
  - Atlantic Coast Terminal Company, minute book (7b), 1920-1935 (Volume 8)
  - Atlantic Development Company, minute book (8), 1902-1904 (Volume 9)
  - Berkeley Street Railway Company, general ledger (11), 1902-1906 (Volume 10)
  - Berkeley Street Railway Company, minute book (15), 1897-1904 (Volume 11)
  - Berkeley Street Railway Company, minute book (16), 1904-1906 (Volume 12)
  - Blue Ridge Power Company, cash journal (7B-1), 1914-1916 (Volume 13)
  - Blue Ridge Power Company, board of directors' and stockholders' minute book (7J-1), 1914-1921 (Volume 14)
  - Brook Turnpike Company, cash-only journal (36), 1906-1915 (Volume 15)
  - Brook Turnpike Company, corporate history (39), 1899-1915 (Volume 16)
  - Brook Turnpike Company, general ledger (30), 1889-1904 (Volume 17)
  - Brook Turnpike Company, general ledger (31), 1904-1906 (Volume 18)
  - Brook Turnpike Company, general ledger (32), 1906-1909 (Volume 19)
  - Brook Turnpike Company, receiver's record (33), 1899-1905 (Volume 20)
  - Brook Turnpike Company, receiver's record (34), 1905-1906 (Volume 21)
  - Brook Turnpike Company, receiver's record and journal (35), 1904-1905 (Volume 22)
  - Brook Turnpike Company, board of directors' and stockholders' minute book (39a), 1899-1915 (Volume 23)
  - Brook Turnpike Company, stock ledger (38), 1892-1902 (Volume 24)
  - Brookland Railway and Improvement Company, board of directors' and stockholders' minute book (29a), 1892-1916 (Volume 25)
  - Brookland Railway and Improvement Company, board of directors' and stockholders' minute book (29b), 1917-1925 (Volume 26)
  - Brookland Railway and Improvement Company, cash book and journal (21), 1904 (Volume 27)
  - Brookland Railway and Improvement Company, cash journal (20), 1892-1900 (Volume 28)
  - Brookland Railway and Improvement Company, general ledger (18), 1904-1917 (Volume 29)
  - Brookland Railway and Improvement Company, general ledger (19), 1917-1927 (Volume 30)
  - Brookland Railway and Improvement Company, ledger (17), 1893-1895 (Volume 31)
  - Brookland Railway and Improvement Company, receiver's journal (22), 1904-1907 (Volume 32)
  - Brookland Railway and Improvement Company, receiver's journal (23), 1907-1910 (Volume 33)
  - Brookland Railway and Improvement Company, receiver's journal (24), 1910-1913 (Volume 34)
  - Brookland Railway and Improvement Company, receiver's journal (25), 1913-1916 (Volume 35)
  - Brookland Railway and Improvement Company, receiver's journal (26), 1917-1920 (Volume 36)
  - Brookland Railway and Improvement Company, receiver's journal (27), 1920-1925 (Volume 37)
  - Brookland Railway and Improvement Company, receiver's journal (28), 1925-1927 (Volume 38)
  - Charlottesville and Albemarle Railway Company, board of directors' and stockholders' minute book (8-J-1), 1900-1903 (Volume 39)
  - Charlottesville and Albemarle Railway Company, board of directors' and stockholders' minute book (9-J-1), 1903-1913 (Volume 40)
  - Charlottesville and Albemarle Railway Company, board of directors' and stockholders' minute book (9-J-2), 1913-1923 (Volume 41)
  - Chesapeake Park Corporation, board of directors' and stockholders' minute book (40a), 1913-1920 (Volume 42)
  - Chesapeake Park Corporation, general ledger (40), 1912-1920 (Volume 43)
  - Citizens Appliance Corporation, minute book (11-J-1), 1924-1928 (Volume 44)
  - Citizens Railway, Light and Power Company, board of directors' minute book (12-J2-1), 1900-1909 (Volume 45)
  - Citizens Railway, Light and Power Company, board of directors' minute book (12-J2-2), 1909-1913 (Volume 46)
  - Citizens Railway, Light and Power Company, board of directors' minute book (12-J2-3), 1913- (Volume 47)
  - Citizens Railway, Light and Power Company, stockholders' minute book (12-J1-1), 1900-1909 (Volume 48)
  - Citizens Railway, Light and Power Company, stockholders' minute book (12-J1-2), 1909-1913 (Volume 49)
  - City Gas Company of Norfolk, board of directors' minute book (80-E), 1896-1923 (Volume 50)
  - City Gas Company of Norfolk, board of directors' minute book (80-F), 1924-1927 (Volume 51)
  - City Gas Company of Norfolk, board of directors' and stockholders' minute book (80-D), 1916-1927 (Volume 52)
  - City Gas Company of Norfolk, board of directors' and stockholders' minute book (80-H), 1928-1930 (Volume 53)
  - City Gas Company of Norfolk, executive committee minute book (80-G), 1896 (Volume 54)
  - City Gas Company of Norfolk, Legal Department copies of meeting minutes of board of directors and stockholders (80-I), 1926-1929 (Volume 55)
  - City Gas Company of Norfolk, Legal Department copies of meeting minutes of board of directors and stockholders (80-J), January-June 1930 (Volume 56)
  - City Gas Company of Norfolk, stockholders' minute book (80-C), 1896-1915 (Volume 57)
  - City Gas Light Company of Norfolk (earliest known as City Gas Association of Norfolk), board of directors' and stockholders' minute book (84), 1849-1883 (Volume 58)
  - City Gas Light Company of Norfolk, board of directors' and stockholders' minute book (85), 1884-1896 (Volume 59)
  - City Gas Light Company of Norfolk, cash journal B (82), 1865-1888 (Volume 60)
  - City Gas Light Company of Norfolk, cash journal C (83), 1889-1896 (Volume 61)
  - Clifton Forge Public Service Company, cash journal (15-B-1), 1907-1913 (Volume 62)
  - Clifton Forge Public Service Company, common stock ledger (15-K-1), 1910-1913 (Volume 63)
  - Clifton Forge Public Service Company, general ledger (15-A-1), 1907-1913 (Volume 64)
  - Clifton Forge Public Service Company, minute book (15-J-1), 1911-1913 (Volume 65)
  - Clifton Forge Public Service Company (Virginia Western Electric Company - merged), minute book (15-J-2), 1911-1913 (Volume 66)
  - Commonwealth Ice Company, board of directors' and stockholders' minute book (93a), 1926-1935 (Volume 67)
  - Commonwealth Ice Company, general ledger (86), 1926-1936 (Volume 68)
  - Commonwealth Ice Company, voucher register (87), 1926-1928 (Volume 69)
  - Covington Light and Power Company, minute book (16-J-1), 1912-1913 (Volume 70)
  - Delpen Corporation, cash journal (95), 1911-1915 (Volume 71)
  - Delpen Corporation, cash journal (96), 1916-1920 (Volume 72)
  - Delpen Corporation, general ledger (94), 1911-1920 (Volume 73)
  - Electric Company of Virginia, cash journal (97), 1894-1898 (Volume 74)
  - Electric Generating Company, board of directors' and stockholders' minute book (101), 1909-1910 (Volume 75)
  - Electric Generating Company, cash journal (99), 1910-1914 (Volume 76)
  - Electric Generating Company, general ledger (98), 1909-1914 (Volume 77)
  - Electric Light and Power Company, Inc. of Remington, board of directors' and stockholders' minute book (52-J-1), 1921-1927 (Volume 78)
  - Elizabeth Night Ferry Company, minute book (102), 1897-1899 (Volume 79)
  - Elizabeth River and Hampton Roads Ferry, board of directors' and stockholders' minute book (105), 1899-1912 (Volume 80)
  - Elizabeth River and Hampton Roads Ferry, general ledger (103), 1907-1909 (Volume 81)
  - Emporia Hydroelectric Power Company, board of directors' and stockholders' minute book (19-J-1), 1909-1925 (Volume 82)
  - Emporia Hydroelectric Power Company, cash journal (19-B-1), 1909-1925 (Volume 83)
  - Emporia Hydroelectric Power Company, general ledger (19-A-1), 1909-1925 (Volume 84)
  - Fairfax and Loudoun Light and Power Company, board of directors' and stockholders' minute book (20-J-1), 1922-1925 (Volume 85)
  - Fredericksburg Electric Company, board of directors' and stockholders' minute book (108), 1909-1910 (Volume 86)
  - Fredericksburg Electric Company, cash journal (107), 1910-1914 (Volume 87)
  - Fredericksburg Electric Company, ledger (106), 1910-1914 (Volume 88)
  - Fredericksburg Electric Company, stockholders' minute book (113), 1904-1914 (Volume 89)
  - Fredericksburg Power Company, board of directors' and stockholders' minute book (114), 1906-1914 (Volume 90)
  - Fredericksburg Power Company, cash journal (110), 1906-1912 (Volume 91)
  - Fredericksburg Power Company, cash journal (111), 1912-1914 (Volume 92)
  - Fredericksburg Power Company, ledger (109), 1906-1914 (Volume 93)
  - General Motor Company, minute book (114a), 1915 (Volume 94)
  - Greenbrier Power Company, board of directors' and stockholders' minute book (22J-1), 1917-1925 (Volume 95)
  - Greenbrier Power Company, company 22 cash journal (22B-1), 1917-1923 (Volume 96)
  - Greenbrier Power Company, ledger (22A-1), 1917-1923 (Volume 97)
  - Halifax Power Company, board of directors' minute book (23J-2-1), 1921-1925 (Volume 98)
  - Halifax Power Company, minute book of meeting providing for the merger to Southside Virginia Power Company (23J1-2), October 1925 (Volume 99)
  - Halifax Power Company, stockholders' minute book (23J1-1), 1921-1925 (Volume 100)
  - Hampton Towing Corporation, board of directors' and stockholders' minute book (27J-1), 1917-1935 (Volume 101)
  - Hampton Towing Corporation, board of directors' and stockholders' minute book (27J-2), 1936-1942 (Volume 102)
  - Highland Park Company, board of directors' and stockholders' minute book (120A), 1890-1928 (Volume 103)
  - Highland Park Company, board of directors' and stockholders' minute book (120B), 1928-1935 (Volume 104)
  - Highland Park Company, cash journal (116), 1904-1909 (Volume 105)
  - Highland Park Company, cash journal (117), 1909-1914 (Volume 106)
  - Highland Park Company, cash journal (118), 1915-1921 (Volume 107)
  - Highland Park Company, cash journal (119), 1921-1927 (Volume 108)
  - Highland Park Company, cash journal (119A), 1927-1935 (Volume 109)
  - Highland Park Company, general ledger (115), 1904-1917 (Volume 110)
  - Hydroelectric Corporation of Virginia, board of directors' and stockholders' minute book (763), 1929-1939 (Volume 111)
  - Hydroelectric Corporation of Virginia, board of directors' and stockholders' minute book (764), 1939-1952 (Volume 112)
  - Hydroelectric Corporation of Virginia, cash daybook (757), 1929-1939 (Volume 113)
  - Hydroelectric Corporation of Virginia, cash daybook (758), 1940-1952 (Volume 114)
  - Hydroelectric Corporation of Virginia, general ledger (756A), 1929-1939 (Volume 115)
  - Intramural Railway Company, board of directors' and stockholders' minute book (121), 1907 (Volume 116)
  - James River Construction Company, board of directors' and stockholders' minute book (126), 1898-1901 (Volume 117)
  - Knightly Light and Power Company, board of directors' and stockholders' minute book (30-J-1), 1925-1932 (Volume 118)
  - Leesburg Electric Company, board of directors' and stockholders' minute book (31-J-1), 1902-1930 (Volume 119)
  - Leesburg Electric Company, general accounts ledger (31-A-5), 1929 (Volume 120)
  - Loudoun Light and Power Company, board of directors' and stockholders' minute book (32-J-1), 1912-1923 (Volume 121)
  - Loudoun Light and Power Company, board of directors' and stockholders' minute book (32-J-2), 1923-1929 (Volume 122)
  - Loudoun Light and Power Company, board of directors' and stockholders' minute book (32-J-3), 1929-1935 (Volume 123)
  - Louisa County Light and Power Company, minute book (33-J-1), 1925-1929 (Volume 124)
  - Manchester Railway and Improvement Company, minute book (129), 1887-1903 (Volume 125)
  - Meadow Creek Corporation, bi-annual cash journal (768), 1937-1952 (Volume 126)
  - Meadow Creek Corporation, board of directors' and stockholders' minute book (772), 1937-1952 (Volume 127)
  - Meadow Creek Corporation, general accounts ledger (766), 1937-1946 (Volume 128)
  - Meadow Creek Corporation, general accounts ledger (767), 1947-1952 (Volume 129)
  - Middle Virginia Power Company, board of directors' and stockholders' minute book (35-J-1), 1925-1937 (Volume 130)
  - Middle Virginia Power Company, board of directors' and stockholders' minute book (35-J-2), 1938-1942 (Volume 131)
  - National Gas Company, board of directors' and stockholders' minute book (130A), 1901-1904 (Volume 132)
  - National Gas Company (Berkeley Division), cash journal (130B), 1902-1904 (Volume 133)
  - New Mechanicsville Turnpike Company, cash book (133), 1904-1905 (Volume 134)
  - New Mechanicsville Turnpike Company, cash journal (132), 1904-1908 (Volume 135)
  - New Mechanicsville Turnpike Company, ledger (131), 1904-1905 (Volume 136)
  - Newport News and Hampton Railway, Gas and Electric Company, annual financial summary (38H-1-2), 1914-1921 (Volume 137)
  - Newport News and Hampton Railway, Gas and Electric Company, board of directors' minute book (38-J2-1), 1913-1920 (Volume 138)
  - Newport News and Hampton Railway, Gas and Electric Company, board of directors' minute book (38-J2-2), 1920-1926 (Volume 139)
  - Newport News and Hampton Railway, Gas and Electric Company, cash book and check register (38-C1-1), 1914 (Volume 140)
  - Newport News and Hampton Railway, Gas and Electric Company, stockholders' minute book (38-J1-1), 1913-1926 (Volume 141)
  - Newport News and Old Point Railway and Electric Company, board of directors' minute book (39-J2-1), 1898-1907 (Volume 142)
  - Newport News and Old Point Railway and Electric Company, board of directors' minute book (39-J2-2), 1907-1913 (Volume 143)
  - Newport News and Old Point Railway and Electric Company, stockholders' minute book (39-J1-1), 1898-1914 (Volume 144)
  - Newport News Gas Company, board of directors' minute book (37-J2-1), 1897-1913 (Volume 145)
  - Newport News Gas Company, capital stock register (37-K2), 1897-1913 (Volume 146)
  - Newport News Gas Company, stock ledger (37-K1), 1897-1913 (Volume 147)
  - Newport News Gas Company, stockholders' minute book (37-J1-1), 1907-1913 (Volume 148)
  - Norfolk and Atlantic Terminal Company, board of directors' and stockholders' minute book (150A), 1893-1901 (Volume 149)
  - Norfolk and Atlantic Terminal Company, board of directors' and stockholders' minute book (150B), 1901-1908 (Volume 150)
  - Norfolk and Atlantic Terminal Company, board of directors' and stockholders' minute book (150C), 1908-1911 (Volume 151)
  - Norfolk and Atlantic Terminal Company, cash journal (140), 1893-1901 (Volume 152)
  - Norfolk and Atlantic Terminal Company, cash journal (141), 1901-1907 (Volume 153)
  - Norfolk and Atlantic Terminal Company, cash journal (142), 1907-1911 (Volume 154)
  - Norfolk and Atlantic Terminal Company, general ledger (139) 1892-1911 (Volume 155)
  - Norfolk and Atlantic Terminal Company, general ledger (134), 1900-1901 (Volume 156)
  - Norfolk and Atlantic Terminal Company, ledger (138), 1903-1907 (Volume 157)
  - Norfolk and Ocean View Railroad and Hotel Company, board of directors' and stockholders' minute book (172), 1884-1896 (Volume 158)
  - Norfolk and Ocean View Railroad Company, cash journal (166), 1909-1913 (Volume 159)
  - Norfolk and Ocean View Railroad Company, cash journal (167), 1913-1918 (Volume 160)
  - Norfolk and Ocean View Railway Company, executive committee minute book (171), 1907-1919 (Volume 161)
  - Norfolk and Ocean View Railway Company, general ledger (161), 1898-1899 (Volume 162)
  - Norfolk and Ocean View Railway Company, general ledger (162), 1899-1900 (Volume 163)
  - Norfolk and Ocean View Railway Company, ledger (165), 1907-1923 (Volume 164)
  - Norfolk and Portsmouth Traction Company, board of directors' minute book (197), 1906-1911 (Volume 165)
  - Norfolk and Portsmouth Traction Company, common and preferred stock ledger (210), 1910-1911 (Volume 166)
  - Norfolk and Portsmouth Traction Company, common stock ledger (206-207), 1910-1911 (Volume 167-168)
  - Norfolk and Portsmouth Traction Company, common stock register (209), 1910-1911 (Volume 169)
  - Norfolk and Portsmouth Traction Company, common stock transfers ledger (215), 1906-1910 (Volume 170)
  - Norfolk and Portsmouth Traction Company, common stock transfers ledger (216), 1910 (Volume 171)
  - Norfolk and Portsmouth Traction Company, construction and equipment committee minute book (203), 1907-1908 (Volume 172)
  - Norfolk and Portsmouth Traction Company, executive committee minute book (199), 1906-1907 (Volume 173)
  - Norfolk and Portsmouth Traction Company, executive committee minute book (200), 1907-1908 (Volume 174)
  - Norfolk and Portsmouth Traction Company, executive committee minute book (201), 1908-1909 (Volume 175)
  - Norfolk and Portsmouth Traction Company, executive committee minute book (202), 1909-1910 (Volume 176)
  - Norfolk and Portsmouth Traction Company, general ledger (183), 1906-1908 (Volume 177)
  - Norfolk and Portsmouth Traction Company, monthly cash journal (185), 1906-1907 (Volume 178)
  - Norfolk and Portsmouth Traction Company, monthly cash journal (186), 1907-1908 (Volume 179)
  - Norfolk and Portsmouth Traction Company, monthly cash journal (187), 1909-1910 (Volume 180)
  - Norfolk and Portsmouth Traction Company, monthly cash journal (188), 1910-1911 (Volume 181)
  - Norfolk and Portsmouth Traction Company, preferred stock ledger (211), 1910-1911 (Volume 182)
  - Norfolk and Portsmouth Traction Company, preferred stock transfers ledger (217), 1910-1911 (Volume 183)
  - Norfolk and Portsmouth Traction Company, stock ledger (214), 1906-1910 (Volume 184)
  - Norfolk and Portsmouth Traction Company, stock ledger (205), 1910 (Volume 185)
  - Norfolk and Portsmouth Traction Company, stockholders' minute book (198), 1906-1911 (Volume 186)
  - Norfolk and Portsmouth Traction Company, stockholders' record book (218), 1906-1911 (Volume 187)
  - Norfolk and Portsmouth Traction Company, various committees' minute book (204), 1906-1911 (Volume 188)
  - Norfolk and Willoughby Spit and Old Point Railroad Company, board of directors' minute book (245), 1896-1899 (Volume 189)
  - Norfolk City Railroad Company, board of directors' and stockholders' minute book (152A), 1866-1871 (Volume 190)
  - Norfolk City Railroad Company, board of directors' and stockholders' minute book (153), 1886-1889 (Volume 191)
  - Norfolk City Railroad Company, board of directors' and stockholders' minute book (154), 1888-1894 (Volume 192)
  - Norfolk City Railroad Company, cash book (152), 1887-1894 (Volume 193)
  - Norfolk City Railroad Company, ledger (151), 1887-1895 (Volume 194)
  - Norfolk Gas and Electric Company, stockholders' minute book (155), 1896 (Volume 195)
  - Norfolk Heat, Light and Power Company, board of directors' and stockholders' minute book (160), 1899-1911 (Volume 196)
  - Norfolk Heat, Light and Power Company, monthly cash journal (157), 1902-1904 (Volume 197)
  - Norfolk Heat, Light and Power Company, stock ledger (159), 1899-1902 (Volume 198)
  - Norfolk, Portsmouth and Newport News Company, board of directors' minute book (180), 1900-1906 (Volume 199)
  - Norfolk, Portsmouth and Newport News Company, board of directors' minute book (182), 1900-1905 (Volume 200)
  - Norfolk, Portsmouth and Newport News Company, ledger (173), 1902-1904 (Volume 201)
  - Norfolk, Portsmouth and Newport News Company, ledger (174), 1905-1906 (Volume 202)
  - Norfolk, Portsmouth and Newport News Company, monthly cash journal (176), 1905-1906 (Volume 203)
  - Norfolk, Portsmouth and Newport News Company, stockholders' minute book (181), 1900-1906 (Volume 204)
  - Norfolk Railway and Light Company, board of directors' minute book (233), 1899-1920 (Volume 204a)
  - Norfolk Railway and Light Company, board of directors' minute book (234), 1920-1927 (Volume 205)
  - Norfolk Railway and Light Company, board of directors' and stockholders' minute book (237), 1906-1910 (Volume 206)
  - Norfolk Railway and Light Company, board of directors' and stockholders' minute book and bylaws (236), 1926-1927 (Volume 207)
  - Norfolk Railway and Light Company, common stock ledger (232A), 1906-1925 (Volume 208)
  - Norfolk Railway and Light Company, common stock ledger (232B), 1910-1919 (Volume 209)